Life can be a comedy or a tragedy, it all depends on how you look at it.
Melinda and Melinda is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Woody Allen.
While dining out with friends, Sy suggests the
difficulty of separating comedy from tragedy.
To illustrate his point, he tells his guests two parallel stories about Melinda ; both versions have the same basic
elements, but one take on her state of affairs leans toward levity, while the other is full of anguish.
Each story involves Melinda coping with a recent divorce through substance abuse
while beginning a romantic relationship with a close friend's husband.
Ellis Moonsong, played by Chiwetel Ejiofor.
Hobie, played by Will Ferrell.
Lee, played by Jonny Lee Miller.
Melinda Robicheaux, played by Radha Mitchell.
Susan, played by Amanda Peet.
Laurel, played by Chloë Sevigny.
Melinda and Melinda is a 2004 American comedy-drama
film written and directed by Woody Allen.
The film is set in Manhattan and stars Radha Mitchell as the protagonist
Melinda, in two storylines; one tragic and the other comic.
It premiered at the 2004 San Sebastián International Film Festival and was given a limited
theatrical release in the United States on March 18, 2005, by Fox Searchlight Pictures.
The film explores themes of married couple, friends,
falling in love, celebration, blunt.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.